https://regularguy.com/privacy/

Skip to content
December 11, 2020
Home “God – Family – Country”
Links
Home “God – Family – Country”
Links
Search for:
OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Last Update: 03/16/2018
We are committed to advising you of the right to your privacy and strive to provide a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Policy sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to our website.
By using out website, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personally identifiable information [PII] and non-personally identifiable [Non-PII] information about you in the manner described in this policy. Please read this Statement carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities under the law. If you disagree or do not accept with the way we collect and process your PII or Non-PII, please do not use this website.
Scope of this Policy
This policy applies to this website and regulates the processing of PII provided by you and Non-PII collected by us during your visit to our Website. It describes what type of information we collect; how we use that information and to whom we can provide that information. It also informs you of how to notify us to stop collecting and providing your information. We are located in the United States and by registering on our website, you agree to be governed by the laws of the United States.
Our website predominantly contains links to third party websites over which we have no control. As such, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites when you choose to link to them from our website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of those third party websites to understand how they collect, use and share your information.
Information We Collect and Retain
We collect the following general types of information about you when you contact us regarding our website:
Personally identifiable information [PII]: is information that can be used to personally identify you. We do not collect PII.
Behavioral information: is information pertaining to how you use our website; the areas of our website that you visit; what ads or services you accessed; and information about your computer hardware and software including your IP address, geographic location, browser preference, operating system type, domain names, times that you access the internet and other website you have been referred to us through. This information is necessary to analyze the use of resources, troubleshooting problems, preventing fraud, and improving our services and products.
Web technology information: is information we automatically collect from you when you open one of our emails or visit our Website. This includes information collected from the use of cookies, web beacons or java script as discussed below.
No Information Collected from Children: We never knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected Personally Identifiable Information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no information regarding its use or disclose to third parties.
Use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and Java Script
Cookies: “Cookies” are a feature in your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of our Website. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content or links you view or may have viewed on past visits. When you visit our site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your past viewing history or the email or site that directed you to our Website. You can disable cookies, although the website may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. In order to use all of the features and functionality of our Website, you need to accept cookies.
Removing Cookies: You have the ability to accept, decline or remove cookies at any time by modifying your browser settings. Please see http://cookiecentral.com. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our website. The National Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) offers an opt-out tool (located at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managin/opt_out.asp) for the purpose of allowing consumers to “opt-out” of the behavioural advertising delivered by its member companies. Some of the third parties with whom we have entered into contractual arrangements are members of NAI.
Web Beacons: We also use electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs, clear gifs or action tags) that allow us to collect certain information about your visit to these Web pages (including the number of users who have visited those pages). This measures and improves the effectiveness of advertisements and delivery of services. Web beacons are not used to access your PII; they are a technique used to compile aggregated statistics about website usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of page view and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. This information may be shared with one or more third parties so that they can understand the types of visitors to our website; how those visitors use our website; and the effectiveness of advertisements. We may also use web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in our database.
Disabling Web Beacons: Because web beacons are the same as any other content request, you cannot opt out or refuse them. However, they can be rendered ineffective by either opting out of cookies or changing the cookie setup in your browser.
JavaScript: We may also use JavaScript within certain advertisements. JavaScript is a computer language that enhances the functionality of our website, particularly with respect to pictures. We do not collect any PII through JavaScript but use it to analyze and improve our website’s functions.
Disabling JavaScript: You may deactivate JavaScript via your browser settings or activate it the same way. If you disable JavaScript you will not be able to use some of the functions of our website.
IP Addresses: Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) is a unique Internet “address” which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider (“ISP”). For local area network (“LAN”), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by web servers and collect information about a user’s traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the web. Your IP address can reveal what geographic area you are connecting from and which ISP you are using. We automatically track certain information based upon your actions on our website. We may use this information to do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from and which URL you next go to after visiting our website, your computer browser information in addition to your IP address.
Computer Profiles: We may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the experience of our visitors. For instance, we may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with PII, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you.
How We Use the Information Collected
Providing Services: We use the information we gather on our Website for the purposes of providing the services or advertisement you have requested. This may include passing your information on to a third party who we have a contract to provide such services. Although our contractual arrangement limits how such third party can use your information, we do not control the privacy practices of this third party. If you have any questions or wish to remove your information from the third party’s database, you will need to contact that party directly.
Improving our Website: We also use the information we gather on our Website to respond to any inquires you make; operate and improve our Website, improve and create a positive user experience on our website; and deliver the services you requested from our Website. Our services include the display of personalized products, content, and advertising relating to your experience and interests. The information we gather on our Website may be shared with other companies under common ownership with ours throughout the world or our Advertisers.
Disclosure of Information to Others
We disclose to third parties throughout the world your combined the information we collect, as set forth below:
Service Delivery and Vendors: We share your information with third parties who help us in the delivery the services you have requested. We disclose your information to companies and individuals we employ to perform technical functions on our behalf. Examples include third parties who host our website, analyze our data, provide marketing assistance and provide customer service. These companies and individuals may not share that information with any other third party or use that data for any other purpose.
Anonymous information: We may also share aggregated anonymous information about you and other persons using our website with third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to our website and how those visitors use our website. This includes behavioral information.
Legal Process: We disclose information if legally required to do so, at our discretion or pursuant to a request from a governmental entity, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.
Acquisition or Merger: We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires any or all of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court.
Third Party Use of Your Information
Third parties also collect and use information about you on our Site in the following way:
Advertiser cookies and web beacons: Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on our website and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about you. We do not control the collection techniques of such third parties and have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.
Hyperlinks: Our website and email messages contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the third parties website, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.
Security
We endeavor to safeguard and protect your information. The servers in which we store your are kept in a secure physical environment. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. Currently, we use Secure Socket Layer Software (“SSL”) to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including names and addresses as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although we take commercially reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot and do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through this site is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.
Changes to Privacy Statement
We reserve the right to make material changes to the substance of this Privacy Statement. We will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.
Search for:
CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Advertising & Marketing
Breaking News
Congress
Donald Trump
Health & Wellness
Holocaust
Contact
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
